Commanders family, the moment we have
all been waiting for. We've got our
newest commander and we have the whole
crew on deck to break down Washington's
first round selection in the 2026 NFL
draft. And I had the pleasure of
catching up with our newest commander,
Sunny Styles, right after he heard his
name called right out here in
Pittsburgh. And the prospect professor,
Logan Paulson will go inside the film
room with the captain, Big Fletch, to
look at the tape on our newest
linebacker. All that and more right now
on the greatest show in the world,
Command Center.
In the 2026 NFL draft, the Washington
Commanders select Sunny Styles.
>> Sunny Styles with the take down.
>> And you're going to love the game. Going
to be fast, violent, physical. brought
down by St.
>> Told my family this morning I was going
to be a commander.
>> Commander family welcome into Command
Center from out here in Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania for the 2026 NFL draft. I'm
your host Brian Koba Jr. here with Brian
Mitchell and Santana Moss and we just
found out that Sunny Styles went number
seven to the Washington Commanders.
We're bringing a linebacker into the
building fellas. How excited are you to
see Sunny in this defense? Uh
>> very excited. I think we heard the team
say they want to get younger. They want
to get faster. And you look at Sunny.
Yeah. He's a young dude. He's very fast.
He's athletic as hell. I think he helps
out the defense instantly.
>> Yeah. I think one of the things that
stood out to me is just knowing that
where they're going with the defense,
you bring you bringing a new uh D
coordinator. Uh every level we kind of
kind of, you know, made an imp.
You know, the guys up front now in
second second um level and then the
third level brought in the safety and
you know what we have at corner. So,
it's just great to know that we we're
making sure we're playing um you know,
putting a lot of emphasis in saying we
want to make sure we be a better defense
than we were last year.
>> And y'all will be hearing from Sunny
Styles in just a moment. And fellas, I
got to talk to him and interview him and
he said, "This is where I want to be."
He had his manager wearing a burgundy
suit because he said, "I told my parents
this morning that I am going to be a
Washington commander."
speaking into existence, but a guy that
wants to be here. A guy that came into
the building just a couple weeks ago,
saw all the things we had going on,
talked to DQ and said, "You know what?
This is the home for me."
>> I think when you look at this whole
coaching staff and you look at the the
the mindset they had after last year,
listen, that first year, they came in
and did some great things. Last year, I
think we took a step back.
>> Yeah.
>> And then they got new people in the
building and you can see that they are
re reinvigorated. And you see, and I
heard a lot of the players talk about
that. what the feeling they got from the
coaches, the excitement level they got
from the coaches, and if the players
come in with that same level, yeah, I
think big things gonna happen for you.
>> And there's always high expectations for
a first round pick, Tana, as our
resident first round pick.
>> When you got that pick and you walked
into that building on day one, what did
you want to be felt about you? What did
you want to be known about you as that
first round pick?
>> I just wanted to go out there and prove
to them that everything they saw on that
tape was the same thing they're going to
see in person every day. And um I tell
you the truth, I was tearing up all that
stuff where uh whether it was OTAAS's
period or the training camp right up
until I tore my knee. And that's what
went like, "Oh man, this is what I
didn't want to got to go through." But
with all that being said, I think any
guy that's selected that high, they want
to go out there and just prove to that
team, to their teammates that you can
count on me to be that guy, you know,
that I was in college on this level as
well.
>> And you were definitely that guy. And we
have no doubt that Sunny Styles will be
that guy as well. Just like we did for
the pre-draft show, just like we did for
the on the clock show, we nationwide,
baby. We not just out here in
Pittsburgh. We are out at Northwest
Stadium with our crew and the best fans
in the NFL. And we are also out in
Ashurn in the studio. But first, before
we get to all the other good stuff, like
I said, we heard from our number seven
pick, Sunny Styles. I got to interview
him the moment he was picked. Let's
check it out. It's time for best seat in
the house, presented by Siki. The most
disruptive idea in ticketing, a ticket
that works. Expect the expected. See
commanders family here with the number
seven overall pick in the 2026 draft.
Sunny Styles in the building here
looking good in that burgundy and gold
hat. My brother, first things first.
Congratulations.
>> Yeah, I appreciate it. I'm blessed. I
just want to give all the glory to God,
man. Super excited. Can't wait to get to
Washington and get to work.
>> Amen. Amen. And you were overcome with
emotion when you found out about that
pick, man. What hit you in that moment?
Because you knew you were going at some
point tonight, but that emotion still
hit, man. What was that about?
>> Man, you know, I had a lot of great
visits. Um, you know, but when I was in
that building, it was different. Coach
Noran was different. Coach Jones was
different. Coach Quinn, Mr. Peters,
every meeting just felt different. It
felt right. Felt like they had amazing
people in the building all the way to
like the player development staff.
Everybody was just great people. Um, so
I'm super excited to come to that
building.
>> And you must have been excited cuz even
the crew, you brought Richie rocking the
burgundy suit. So, there's a little bit
of vibes there that maybe you were going
to come to the burgundy and gold. Did
you know that you would be coming here
at number seven?
>> I told my family this morning I was
going to be a commander. Pick seven.
They they told me a bunch of other
teams. I was like, I'm telling you, I
know what it is. I had a gut feeling.
So, I'm just I'm excited it happened.
It's the perfect fit.
>> And you said during your visit, you told
DQ, I hope I'm back here soon. What
about Washington made it the perfect fit
for you,
>> man? Um, I think it's the people that
that's what drew me to Ohio State. You
know, obviously when you're getting
recruited out of college, I mean, out of
high school, you have to pick where you
go. And, uh, the people is what drew me
to Ohio State. And then with the
commanders, it was the people. Um, Coach
Quinn, Mr. Peters, a great man. Coach
Jones a great man. Coach Doran's another
great man. Like everyone I met, like I
said in the building were great people,
great men and women. Um, so that's
really what drew me there. You know, I
think I'm a I'd like to say I'm a good
person and uh I like to surround myself
by other good people. So I'm glad I get
to come into that building.
>> And a lot was made about your
versatility about you being a former
safety, which is wild to think that you
can run a 4-3 being this massive. What
is that versatility and that experience
in multiple positions? Why does that
make you the most dangerous person in
this 2026 NFL draft? Yeah, I think when
you are versatile and can do a multitude
of roles for a defense, it makes the
defense unpredictable, especially as a
coordinator. You have a bunch of
different chess pieces on the board, uh,
it makes you makes you unpredictable,
like I said. Um, you know, I think I can
do a lot of things. And I think the, you
know, the best part about me, I'm just
scratching the surface. Um, you know,
I'm super excited where I'm at right
now, but there's still so much work to
go.
>> And last, but not least, you get to
share this moment with your brother. He
is here at the draft with you, man. How
special is this, not only for you, but
for your family who also sacrificed so
much for you to get to this point? And
me and him been working for this since
we was 5 years old. Um, and I told my
dad, I was like, "Hey, dad, you gonna
cry today." He was like, "Man, I was up
early in the morning, too." He's like,
"This ain't no surprise." Um, so I think
that perspective of it, like, it's no
surprise being here, but, you know,
obviously super blessed and appreciated
to be here.
>> And Sunny, we're going to let you
celebrate cuz we know this is a big
moment for you. We know your brother's
still out there. Last thing, Commanders
fans are all excited to have you here.
Give a message to the fans on what they
can expect to see when Sunny Styles on
the field this year.
>> Man, you getting a guard loves the game.
uh gonna be fast, violent, physical, and
uh get better each and every week and
just help the team win.
>> Amen to that. We love winning, baby.
Command his family here with our number
seven pick at Ohio State, Sunny Styles.
Congratulations, brother.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Man, it was great catching up with Sunny
Styles after he accomplished his dream
of being an NFL player. And fans, we
know you are so excited about this
selection. As we could see and as we
could feel down at Northwest Stadium
when you all heard, the pick was
announced. Now, let's hit it down to our
get loud crew. It's time for your can't
miss moment presented by FanDuel. Make
every moment more with FanDuel, an
official partner of the Washington
Commanders.
>> BC, thank you. We are here at the
Commanders DRAFT PARTY AT NORTHWEST FAN.
>> LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
>> KEEP IT UP.
>> MICHAEL J. Fred Smrs.
>> This night could not have gone any more
perfectly. When the Titans took Cornell
Tour, we looked at each other like we're
getting sunny.
>> No, no, no. WE GOT A CHANCE RIGHT NOW.
BUT IT ACTUALLY STARTED WITH JEREMIAH
LOVE AT THREE. THEN IT WENT THE CARDELL
TAPE. THEN WE SEE THE BIG TRADE. NOW I
GET A LITTLE NERVOUS AND THEN I SAY,
"GUYS, we might have a chance for Sunny
Styles, a Caleb DS." And it was Sunny
Styles.
>> And all I can say is, "Oh, we got a
football player, baby."
>> It was a great night for the Buckeyes,
but we got the one that we wanted. When
you talking about size and speed down
the middle of the field, Sunny can go
sideline to sideline. He can drop. He
can blitz. He can do it all. I think he
our defense changes now.
>> Uh coach Jones got to be just
>> oh my god
>> loving it right now. The different
things that he can do with this guy on
three different levels. The the man
under this guy is so fast. He can track
quarterback and spy quarterbacks. But
the question is ME AND SEAN WAS TALKING
ABOUT IT. HOW FAST DO YOU PUT THE green
dot on his head when they make him call
the plays? Because that's a lot for a
middle linebacker to have to call the
plays and have to check and line people
up.
>> And he's only 21 years old. Yeah, he
doesn't turn 22 until November. So,
you're talking about a kid who's still a
kid and has so much room for growth.
>> Yeah, he got a lot of room for
development. But the best thing about it
is he he's so young that he don't have
bad habits. He's not he's not coming in
where you have to CLEAN STUFF UP. YOU
HAVE TO CATCH HIM UP. But the speed OF
THE GAME WILL NOT CATCH him off guard.
The physicality OF THE GAME WILL NOT
CATCH HIM OFF GUARD DEALING WITH BIG 10
OFFENSIVE LINEMAN. This kid is going to
be a PLUGANDPLAY PLAYER. YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT FOR HIM to
progress. by training camp, by preeason,
this guy should be in the starting
rotation.
>> Day one started instant impact.
>> BUT YOU GOT TO THINK ABOUT IT JUST
BECAUSE HE'S A MENTAL LINEBACKER DON'T
MEAN HE HAS TO START AT MIDDLE
LINEBACKER.
>> He can start at Sam, HE CAN START AT
WILL. He can start at edge if he wanted
to. This guy has a lot to offer any
defense and any defensive coordinator.
>> And you saw what we did with Bobby last
year. him and Frankie both
interchangeable in what they did as far
as
so we got some guys got a lot of
versatility and speed to that defense
>> the last couple of weeks if you think
about it
>> we revealed the new uniforms universally
positive response as expected and now
like this has been a hell OF TWO WEEKS
>> IT HAS IT'S BEEN ONE OF LIKE everything
that we want to happen has happened
we're going to take THAT NEXT STEP WE
TOOK A STEP BACK TO TAKE A STEP FORWARD
WE TOOK A STEP BACK TO GET THE THE REAL
BURGUNDY AND GOLD AND WE STEP FORWARD IN
it and now we step. You say the real
Bergen AND GOLD.
>> THE REAL BURGUNDY AND GOLD. THE ONE THAT
SAYS CHAMPIONSHIPS, THE ONE THAT SAYS
HISTORY, THE ONE THAT SAYS DC AND NOW WE
GOT A NEW PLAYER IN THE BERGEN AND GOLD
THAT'S GOING TO represent it. Well, I
hope he get a chance to wear zero. What
you think? Well, Mikey Mike CAN'T TAKE
>> YOU MONEY TALK.
>> Especially for a couple of Buckeyes. I'm
sure they're going to talk about that.
LET'S TAKE A CLOSER look at the man
wearing zero maybe with the burgundy and
gold. It is time for your winning
numbers presented by the Maryland
Lottery. Please play responsibly. Tony
Styles spent four years in Columbus, but
again only 21 years old. And look at
these career numbers. Nine passes
defended, nine sacks, three force
fumbles, one interception and
athleticism that is off the charts. You
know that is going to translate well the
National Football League. What to be
excited about with the selection? And we
know some guys are even more excited to
break down some of the film on the
newest vendor. It is time for Mission
Ready presented by Big Bear AI. Mission
ready AI for a rapidly evolving world.
Take it away, guys.
>> Finch. Man, I am excited. I think you
are too, right? We got a Buckeye, a
>> and a linebacker, right? Let's take a
look at some of his highlights. This is
from a couple years ago, man, when he's
wearing the number six. They're going to
run a little cross dog here. And I just
love how he chews up ground on this clip
and gets to the quarterback, man. Like I
think about Donte Jones's defense, the
amount of cross talk pressure they run,
and he's just going to be such a weapon
in that department.
>> Yeah. And and that's the the
athleticism. You see the speed. You
talking about eating up space, the 6'5,
uh 446, 40 yard dash, and then the
finish and the tackle when he beats the
uh block of that that running back. This
was two years ago. He's even better now.
>> Yeah. I think that's something that, you
know, we talked about with AP, like he's
every year, every game got better. So,
this doesn't even look like the same guy
that we saw this last season. So, I
mean, he is a special football player.
Love the physicality. Love the potential
and love the flexibility he brings to
the defense.
>> Yeah, you talked about flexibility. That
leads That's a great segue into this
great segility.
>> And so, again, like he's up in the line
of scrimmage, man. I don't know a lot of
players that I watch in this college
cycle who have the kind of range to get
all the way over. This is college hashes
now. Fletch, look at the amount of space
he has to cover to get over here to
match this hitch route.
>> And and and you mentioned a lot of
players not doing that.
>> Most guys would be panicked. They would
panic. They wouldn't feel comfortable
staying that a gap as long as he stayed
in that a gap and knowing he had to get
like you said all the way to that
college ass. And what I what I love
about it, he arrives violently and and
making a play.
>> Put that Ryell on him. Give him that
touch.
>> Ryell. That was a little little forearm
for shoulder. I like that.
>> Yeah. Taking it back to the good old
days there, Fletch. Huh.
>> Body of B linebacker.
>> So, and then we we've seen this clip,
but this is, I think, something that is
underutilized from him, right? Everyone
talks about, you know, like what can he
do and what can he be here? He is on the
edge here. And I see a guy like, again,
this is an NFL tackle. This guy's
playing for the Philadelphia Eagles
right now and this is a speed rush
around the edge. Little cross shop there
and finish at the quarterback. Think
about him in that Van Ginko role, right?
Everyone thinks, "Oh, I'm going to play
off ball middle linebacker." I think
there's more of a defensive weapon here
in my opinion.
>> And this is a situation where you're
like, "Where's Waldo?" Oh, I love that.
>> Where's Sunny? One minute he's outside,
one minute he's off the ball, one minute
he's off the edge. Is he rushing? Is he
dropping? No. This time he's beating
your your your right tackle for a sack.
And just the versatility. I love this.
>> And I love that you said where's Waldo
cuz you got Leo Chanel who can play
inside, outside, right? You got Frankie
Luvu, right? And now, so now I think
about like how as an offense, how do we
target protections, man? We've got
dynamic play makers at the second level
of this defense. And don't forget, he's
a converted safety. There are clips of
him covering and running down the post.
Man, I I just think that gives you so
much flexibility on defense.
>> It's so much flexibility. And that's the
key when you talk about Donte Jones
defense. Flexibility, position flex. And
we got to get to the next play because
the NEXT PLAY THIS IS my bad. THIS IS
THIS IS my favorite play right here.
>> Dude, I have I have flashbacks of you
doing this to me when we played
together, right? So watch our guy right
here. This guard thinks this guard is
like, "Man, I got an easy job. I'm going
to go up here, block this guy, converted
safety, and you see a mentality, Fletch,
a physicality, which gets me a little
bit juiced up."
>> Oh, yeah. And I love the downhill the
shot. We call that a shock and shed.
Just look how he he hits that line.
lineman. That's almost like Baptist.
Wow.
>> You see the head goes back.
>> I love when you see that bobblehead
>> step when the head goes back. He's done.
Now get greedy.
>> Yeah.
>> Take him off. Get greedy. Become part of
the tackle tackler. That's textbook
linebacker play. Take on the lineman.
Now stay block defeating the block and
making a play.
>> And Fletch, I keep thinking while we're
talk, these are good football plays,
man. But I keep seeing number six on
here. He wore number zero when he was at
his best in 2025 against Miami against
these big time football clubs. So, he is
just going to get better. Oh, yeah. And
I can't wait to see it, man. It's going
to be so exciting to watch him in the
Shironte Jones defense. Back to you, BC.
>> Welcome back into Command Center from
out here in Pittsburgh at the 2026 NFL
draft. I'm here with some fly guys. And
fellas, we talked about it when we were
on the clock about what Sunny Styles
could do in this defense. Be miss, let's
reiterate that a little bit. How does he
fit in our new look defense? Well, I
think the thing about him is a guy you
can put in the middle and Sunny Sal
could be the guy where he comes across
and cover. Uh, you look at the whole
linebacker core, it seemed to be new.
You know, him Chanel McGee now can take
that step. It's a lot of different
things they can do here. But the thing
about him, he brings that great
athleticism. He's bring versatility. And
when you got a guy like that, you can
use him in different ways. I listen I
still think at 6'5 he can get some pass
rush move and you can play him inside
outside different things you can do with
a guy like that and I'm expecting Donte
Jones to go out there and say you know
what dude
>> we going to open up something else with
you we're going to make you even more of
a of a deadly weapon out there.
>> Hey I couldn't wait to see it because
after watching Minnesota attack us last
year when we played them and seeing how
they linebackers was moving around. I
mean, I'm having visions of that now
with Chanel Styles, you know, uh, you
name it. Um, uh, Jordan, Jordan McGee,
like Louu, all those guys. Like, I mean,
we have so many talented guys. So, just
to see this young guy be able to fit
into that package. I can't wait to see
it cuz, you know, right now we're just
high on draft pick, but I can't wait to
really see him line up out there with
all the other guys. I would love to be a
fly on the wall when they start putting
this defense together with all this this
different talent they've added with free
agency and drafting him tonight.
>> And that has to be love to Donte Jones,
a first time defensive coordinator. You
say, "Okay, what kind of guys do you
like in this defense?" We're going to go
get you that guy. You want a versatile
hitter, we got you a young, versatile
hitter right there. Donte Jones has to
be elated.
>> He has to be elated. But I I can tell
you this,
>> Jaden Daniels would be a lady, too.
Because
>> with that, the different people they've
added, that means the defense can be
better. The defense can take the ball,
give it back to him more.
>> You know, people always just think you
got to go on the offensive side. This
defense can be very, very, very helpful
to this offense.
>> And you guys mentioned the guys like
McGee, like Louvu, even Kane Madron.
There are a lot of linebackers on this
roster. We've heard them big up guys
like McGee and Louvu. How do you feel
this pick changes the way we use them in
this defense? Cuz again, they're
versatile as well.
>> Well, you know what? They can't keep
everybody.
>> And what I love about it,
>> if all these dudes believe in
themselves, as they should, I know like
Tanner did, like I did,
>> you should have some hell of competition
and you and the best four the best five
to six win. Yeah.
>> And when you get the best in great
competition, your damn team soarses.
>> It it it raised the level of, you know,
you know, the competition in that room.
and all it does is make everybody else
better, you know, and now now you're
looking for spots to keep guys in
because the because these guys are all
flying around making plays, enough plays
to say, well, I got to see one of these
guys can play special teams, too, so I
can keep them on the roster. So, it's
always good to have that kind of
competition in the room.
>> Competition is great. Iron sharpening
iron and man, we are so excited for this
pick and our guys in the studio back in
Aspen are excited about this pick. so
excited they caught up with our general
manager Adam Peters right after he made
the pick. Time for securing the W
presented by Hercules Fence. Security in
every job.
>> This was an interesting draft and you
ended up with Sunny Styles. At what
point in the process did you kind of peg
him as somebody that you'd like to be a
commander?
>> Yeah, really throughout the whole
process, he was always a guy that was on
our radar. Uh he's he's a special kid.
He's been on the radar for a long time.
He was he was a big-time recruit. He was
a safety that that moved to linebacker a
couple years ago, but you had always
seen him. You always knew who he was.
Even three, four years ago, the the area
scouts that are in there, they know who
Sunny Styles, you know, and that's Sunny
Styles. And then you kind of watch him.
He changed some numbers over the years,
but um you know, he always stood out as
an athlete. And then him becoming a
linebacker the last couple of years, it
was uh it was really cool to see the
evolution. And then um there's just so
much love for him in our building
throughout the process, you know,
starting with our first set of meetings
uh with the college scouts and then with
the coaches and then again as as we got
into the draft meetings and then R&D is
they love him and all his metrics and
and everything and then obviously the
combine to the combine and so you know
the momentum grew and grew and grew and
uh felt really great about it throughout
the whole process until this last week.
really um comfortable, you know, more
than comfortable sitting there and
taking him, but it was just a matter of
was he going to be there.
>> Shout out to our guy AP for knocking it
out the park again. Now, it's time for
Top Five presented by UA Local 5
Plumbers, protecting the health of the
nation's capital since 1890.
Here's a look at the last three players
to be drafted in the first round by our
general manager, Adam Peters, and the
Commanders. Of course, this year, 2026,
the linebacker out of Ohio State, Sunny
Styles, will be a Washington commander.
Then last year, the full-time starter,
offensive tackle Josh Connley Jr. was
drafted in the first round out of
Oregon. And then, of course, the kid in
2024, the number two overall pick,
quarterback Jaden Daniels out of LSU.
Fellas, such an exciting night out here
in Pittsburgh. It's an exciting night
across the nation. We've seen all of our
Commanders crew all over. Now, be to end
the show. You are a resident OG, but you
were also drafted to Washington, man. As
the OG, man, as big aunt. Give advice to
Sunny Styles on how he can get
acclimated in the DMV.
>> Well, I'll tell you this, Sunny. This is
a football uh this this town loves
football. Yeah.
>> And when you come in here, they going to
give you great love. And you just come
in here, do your work, put your head
down, do what you need to do on the
football field. The things you did at
Ohio State, keep doing those same
things. You don't have to change
anything. Just keep being who you are
and growing into your skills and this
they will love you forever. Hell, I've
been here since 1990 and they still love
me in 2026. So just think about it 2050
it could be you
>> and the same thing can be said for
Santana Moss and all of our legends on
command center. Man, it's been so much
fun being out here in Pittsburgh. We got
our newest commander Sunny Styles, the
lineback at Ohio State. We'll catch
y'all next week back in Ashurn on
Command Center. And I'm yours Brian K
Junior here with Brian Mitchell, Santana
Moss, and the rest of the crew all
around the nation. See y'all next week.
Portions of Command Center are filmed at
the Big Bear AI command center studio.
Big Bear AI offers mission ready AI for
a rapidly evolving world, proudly
protecting the Watch Commanders and his
fans.